翻譯：此人已死賽太公  今晚燒紙YY貓  小米山藥  醉芝士
校對：此人已死賽太公  今晚燒紙YY貓 總監   YY貓
后期：加森     時間軸：YY貓
好漢兩個半
第十一季  第八集
早安
Morning.
香脆上校[麥片]
Ooh, Cap'n Crunch.
那是我唯一放進嘴里的"男人"
That's the only man I put in my mouth.
這讓我從另一角度看待我和
It puts my relationship with Orville Redenbacher
奧利華·雷登巴赫[爆米花]的關系
in a whole different light.
我比較喜歡UPS的速遞男
I'm partial to the U.P.S. Guy.
我們這是拿食物開玩笑呢
We're making food jokes here.
UPS速遞男不是食物
The U.P.S. Guy's not food.
他是  前提是在他身上涂一層生奶油
He is if you cover him with whipped cream.
我能說什么呢
What can I say?
女人都迷戀褐色短褲制服里面的壯碩身材
There's just something about a man in brown shorts.
我有大麻煩了
Okay, I'm in big trouble.
一說穿著褐色短褲[內褲]的人  那人就到
Speaking of a man with brown shorts.
怎么了
What's wrong?
剛林賽的男友拉里打給我
Well, I just got a call from Lyndsey's boyfriend Larry.
他說想見我
And he wants to see me.
他是要見杰夫·斯壯曼
Well, he wants to see Jeff Strongman.
誰是杰夫·斯壯曼
Who's Jeff Strongman?
杰夫·斯壯曼是艾倫塑造的另一個自我
Oh, Jeff Strongman is Alan's alter ego
專門用來跟拉里見面和打擊罪犯
he uses to meet Larry and fight crime.
慢著  所以這個假名
Wait, so, you use a fake name
是為了跟其他男人偷情時用的嗎
to sneak around with other men?
你們在哪里認識的  女神卡卡的演唱會嗎
Where do you guys meet? A Lady Gaga concert?
女神卡卡受到眾多同性戀的喜愛
如果你非要知道  是在單車課上
It was a spin class if you must know.
那我現在應該怎么辦
Now, what am I gonna do?
我早告訴你會發生這種事了
I told you something like this was gonna happen.
"我早告訴你會發生這種事了"
"I told you something like this was gonna happen."
我是說真的
Look, I am serious--
他不肯告訴我見面的原因
he wouldn't tell me why he wanted to see me
而且他聽起來很不開心
and he sounded pretty upset.
我們到底生活在什么樣的世界
Well, what kind of world are we living in
居然會有人因為其他男人
where a guy is upset with another guy
睡了他的女朋友而不開心
for banging his girlfriend?
所以我才喜歡當同性戀
See, that's why I love being gay.
男人一旦發現我睡了他的女朋友
A guy finds out I'm doing his girlfriend,
他們不會打電話來罵我
I don't get an angry phone call.
相反我會收到玫瑰花  和交歡時的視頻
I get a dozen roses and a copy of the video.
真可惜  我不能說服拉里我是基
Too bad I can't convince Larry I'm gay.
得了吧  廢柴  我們早被你說服了
Come on, Zippy, you're making it too easy for us.
他來了
There he is.
那個皮膚蒼白的男人
My main man with a winter tan.
杰夫
Jeff.
我給你點了咖啡  你還要其他的嗎
Uh, I got you a coffee. Can I get you anything else?
要不要來個瑪芬蛋糕  麥麩做的哦
Uh, one-one of these muffins? They're bran.
能讓你的身體保持健康哦
Keeps your trains running on time.
-我不餓  -那好吧
- I'm not hungry. - All right then,
我就坐在你對面
I'll just sit across from you.
坐在
Right here...
眾多目擊證人前
in front of all these witnesses.
你知道我女朋友林賽吧
You know my girlfriend Lyndsey?
她叫林賽嗎
Is it Lyndsey?
我以為叫琳達呢
I thought it was Linda.
幸好在我下次見到她前  說清楚
Glad you cleared that up before I saw her again...
不過我見不著她  我干嘛要見她
which I haven't, and why would I?
她背著我偷人
She's been cheating on me.
抱歉  有點噎著了
Mmm, sorry. Just a little...
你為什么覺得她背著你偷人
Why do you think she's cheating on you?
我找了個私家偵探跟蹤她
I hired a private investigator to follow her.
你不介意吧
Uh, do you mind?
她一直去馬里布的別墅跟他私會
She's been meeting him at a house in Malibu.
抱歉  我只是有點震驚
Sorry, sorry, I'm just a little shocked.
想象下我的感受
Imagine how I feel.
想象不到  但我知道
Well, I-I can't, uh, uh, but I do know
在這種情況下  要怪就怪那個女人
that in situations like this, it's the woman who's to blame.
不止該怪她
She's not the only one.
求你了  我還有個兒子要養活
Please, I have a son!
這就是那個奸夫
This is the guy.
-等等  是這家伙嗎  -是的
- Wait, this is the guy? - Yeah.
你認為是這家伙睡了你的女朋友
This is guy you think banging your girlfriend?
我知道是他
I know he is.
只有他
And only him?
沒別人了嗎
Nobody else?
這還不夠糟嗎
Isn't this bad enough?
說的也是
Well, sure.
但應該有其他合理的解釋
But, you know, there could also be another explanation.
我是說  或許是她迷路了
I mean, maybe she's just lost
然后向這家伙問路呢
and she's asking this guy for directions.
是啊  "不好意思  先生
Right, "Excuse me, sir,
能幫我找到去G點的路嗎"
can you help me find my G-spot?"
證據不光是這張照片
It's not just this photo.
晚上出去辦事
It's the late night errands.
把手機藏起來
Hiding her phone.
還有我們好久沒做愛了
Plus, we haven't had sex in forever!
那是挺慘的
Wow, that's rough.
我猜  不管這個男人是誰
I guess this guy, whoever he is,
他滿足了她的所有需求
satisfies her every need.
我想殺了他
I want to kill him.
我討厭被人這樣欺騙
I hate being lied to like this.
我懂
I get it, you know.
有時就是知人知面不知心啊
Sometimes you think you know a person, but you don't.
斯壯曼的意式三文治
Panini for Strongman.
-杰夫  在叫你呢  -什么
- Jeff, that's you. - What?
對  對  是我
Oh, oh, yeah, that's me.
杰夫·斯壯曼
Jeff Strongman.
沒有睡任何人的女朋友
Someone who's not banging anyone's girlfriend.
天啊  我家進了個陌生人
Oh, no, there's a stranger in my house.
可能是70年代同性戀黃片的明星
And it's possibly a gay porn star from the '70s.
是我啦  艾倫
It's me, Alan.
我想你剛說的是
I-I believe you're supposed to say,
"是我啦  馬里奧"
"It's-a me, a-Mario!"
所以你和拉里的會面并不愉快嗎
So, I take it things didn't go great with Larry?
他的確知道了林賽背著他偷人
Well, he does know that Lyndsey's cheating on him,
但好消息是他不知道奸夫是我
but the good news is he doesn't know that it's with me.
那你為什么打扮得像
So, why do you look like one of
穿著便裝的村民樂隊成員
the Village People in street clothes?
村民樂隊是1970年代的經典男子演唱組合
成員分別裝扮成警官  印第安酋長  建筑工人  士兵  摩托車手和牛仔
他找了個私家偵探
Ah, well, uh, he hired a, uh, a private detective,
監視這個房子  因為
uh, to watch the house because, uh,
有意思的地方來了
and here's where it gets really funny,
他認為林賽的奸夫是
he thinks that Lyndsey is cheating on him with...
不是吧
No.
不  不
No, no, no.
不  不  不  這樣不行
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
很扯吧
It's crazy, right?
你干嘛不告訴他真相
Why didn't you tell him the truth?
害怕  膽小
Fear, cowardice.
沒有給牙齒買保險
Lack of a dental plan.
再說了  他都失去林賽了
Uh, besides, he-he just lost Lyndsey,
我不想他再失去他最好的朋友
I didn't want him to lose his best friend.
好吧  如果你不處理好這件事
Okay, well, you're gonna lose your best friend
你會失去你最好的朋友
if you don't fix this!
原來我是你最好的朋友啊
Oh, I'm your best friend?
艾倫  我說真的
Alan, I am serious.
我不想讓私家偵探監視我的房子
I do not want a private detective watching this house.
我也絕對不想
And I... and I definitely don't want
被憤怒的男友追殺
an angry boyfriend after me.
你之前跟林賽上床時
Well, you should've thought of that
就應該想到這一點
before you slept with Lyndsey.
我還有事情要做
I've got some work to do.
我要出去處理點事
And I'm gonna go out and run some errands.
等我回來時  這事最好已經解決了
And when I get back, this better be cleaned up.
別擔心  我馬上處理
Oh, oh, don't worry, I'm on it.
以防萬一
Oh, oh, but just in case.
天啊
Oh, God!
有什么是你這英俊的臉蛋不能駕馭的嗎
Is there any look you can't pull off?
我要殺了你
I'm-a gonna kill you.
你要踢死我啊
What the hell?
艾倫  你在干什么
Alan, what are you doing?
此時此刻  我在找我左邊的蛋蛋
At the moment, looking for my left ball.
拉里剛送我回來  他會看見你的
Larry just dropped me off. He could've seen you.
所以我才來的
That's why I'm here.
拉里覺得你跟沃頓在偷情
Larry thinks you're having an affair with Walden.
什么  他干嘛那樣想
What? Why would he think that?
因為他請的私家偵探
Well, because he he hired a P.I.
拍了一張你們倆在一起的照片
who t a picture of the two of you together.
對了  從照片看那天很冷啊
And by the way, it looked like it was a cold day.
-你個白癡  -我知道
- You're an idiot. - I know.
那我們應該怎么辦
So, what-what are we gonna do?
沒事  這方面我超有經驗
Okay, look, I've done this plenty of times before.
首先要做的就是否認
The first thing you do is deny everything.
好的  否認  等等
Right, denial. Wait.
你這方面超有經驗
You've done this plenty of times before?
你是不是也背著我偷人
Did you ever cheat on me?
沒有
Never.
好的
Okay, good.
是拉里
Oh, it's Larry.
他找你干嘛
What does he want?
我看一下
Uh, well, let's see.
"剛把那個偷人的妓...
Uh, "Just dropped off the cheating whor...
林賽送回家"
Lyndsey."
"想出來喝一杯嗎"
"Want to grab a drink?"
你繼續扮演同情他的好朋友
Okay, you go play the sympathetic friend,
安撫他
calm him down.
我來想辦法
I'll figure something out.
聽起來不錯
Sounds good, uh...
"沒問題  哥們"
"No problem, bro."
加上雞尾酒杯的圖案
Cocktail glass emoji.
-盡量拖延時間  -好的
- Stall him as long as you can. - Right.
很抱歉踢了你蛋蛋
I'm sorry I kicked you in the balls--
你想我怎么補償你
is there anything I can do?
你可以親親它  讓它好受點
You could kiss it and make it better.
再見  艾倫
Good-bye, Alan.
別這樣嘛
Oh, come on!
我自己又親不到
It's not like I could do it myself.
天知道我曾試過
God knows I've tried.
-上車  -羅斯
- Get in the car! - Rose?
你怎么在這里
What are you doing?
有人在跟蹤你
Someone's following you.
沒錯  你嘛
Yeah, you!
沒時間說那么多  你現在很危險
There's no time for this, you're in danger.
沒錯  因為你嘛
Yeah, from you!
快上車吧
Just get in.
我為什么要上你的車
Why would I get in your car?
上一次我試圖相信你
I mean, the last time i tried to trust you...
怎么  你在看什么
What? What are you looking at?
你襯衣上有個小點
You got a little spot on your shirt.
開車  開車  開車
Drive! Drive! Drive!
快開車
Drive! Drive!
我又發現一些新信息
I found out more about this guy.
他的名字是沃頓·施密特
His name is Walden Schmidt.
更像是一噸·特壞屎
More like lying sack of Schmidt.
對不對
Am I right?
原來他是個靠網絡發家的億萬暴發戶
Turns out he's some kind of stupid Internet billionaire.
你不覺得不用為生活而工作的人很討厭嗎
Don't you hate when guys don't work for a living
就像咱倆
like you and me?
沒錯  杰夫·斯壯曼
Amen, Jeff Strongman.
振作點
Hey, come on, you know,
這并不是世界上最糟糕的事
this isn't the worst thing in the world.
你會重新振作起來
You're gonna bounce back.
我早該猜到會有這么一天
I guess, I mean, I should've seen it coming.
她當初就是背著她前男友跟我偷情
I mean, she cheated on her last boyfriend with me.
你是說她前男友
Her-her last boyfriend?
是啊  那個家伙就是個屌絲
Yeah, I guess the guy was a real loser.
白吃白喝的可憐蟲
A pathetic freeloader.
那也只是猜測
Well, that's just conjecture.
也許他是很棒的人
I mean, you know, maybe he's a-a really great guy
而她只是個愛說謊話的賤女人
and she's just a crazy lying bitch.
我不會像她前男友那樣
I'm not gonna take it lying down
娘娘腔似的忍氣吞聲
like the pansy she was dating before me.
"娘娘腔"是你說的  還是她說的
Is "pansy" your word or hers?
她說的
Hers.
我要殺去他們私會的地方
I'm going to the head.
你買單
You get the check
等會我們去會會這個混蛋
and we'll go pay this bastard a visit.
慢慢來
Take your time.
別著急
No rush.
快點  林賽  接電話  快接電話啊
Oh, come on, Lyndsey, pick up, pick up, pick up!
就知道會是語音信箱
Of course, voice mail.
林賽  情況更糟了
Lyndsey, things have gone from bad to worse.
拉里要找沃頓當面對質
Larry is gonna confront Walden,
我不知道該怎么辦
and I don't know what to do.
快回電話
Call me back.
PS  咱倆之間
Oh, and PS-- you and I have
有點小問題需要討論一下
a little issue to discuss ourselves.
PPS  "P"代表"娘娘腔"
Oh, and PPS-- the "P" Stands for "Pansy."
好像甩掉他了
Looks like we lost him.
到底發生什么事了
What the hell is going on?
我很確定拉里雇了一個殺手
Well, I'm pretty sure Larry hired a hit man.
你怎么知道拉里這個人
How do you know about Larry?
因為他在跟蹤你啊
Because he's stalking you.
你怎么知道他在跟蹤我
How do you know that?
因為我在跟蹤你啊
Because I'm stalking you.
好吧  這太荒唐了
Okay, okay, you know, this is ridiculous.
我要報警
I'm calling the police.
你要跟警察說什么
And tell them what?
我們什么證據也沒有
We have no proof of anything.
而且  上次你因為我報警
And besides, how helpful were the police
他們也沒幫上什么忙啊
when you called them on me?
我向警察申請了對你的禁止令
Uh, I got them to issue a restraining order.
你覺得管用嗎
Hi.
好吧  我
Okay, I...
他又來了
Uh-oh, he's back.
我不知道為什么他總能找到我們
I don't know how he keeps finding us.
我來告訴你為什么
I'll tell you how.
我手機上有GPS定位
The GPS on my cell phone.
手機給我
Give me that.
我本來只想關機  不過好吧
I was gonna turn it off, but okay.
抓緊
Hang on.
什么  為什么
What? Why?
應該可以甩掉他了
That ought to do it.
聽我說  這真是胡鬧
Okay, you know... this is nonsense!
送我回家
Take me home.
好吧  送你回家
Okay, homeward bound.
然后被人塞住嘴
And gagged.
折磨好幾天
And tortured for days.
那好吧  送我去酒店
Okay, well, fine, then take me to a hotel.
貝弗利山酒店如何
Beverly Hills Hotel okay?
很好
It's perfect.
砰的一聲  你就被人射死了
And bang, you're dead.
你需要擺脫慣性思維
You need to get off the grid.
去一個他們想不到的地方
Someplace they don't expect you.
也查不到你信用卡的地方
A place they can't track your credit cards.
沒人在查我的信用卡
Nobody is tracking my credit cards.
昨晚你不是還刷卡做了咖啡灌腸嗎
Oh, that wasn't you last night getting a coffee colonic?
我那是為了大腸健康
I will not apologize for a healthy colon.
好了  到了
Okay, here we go.
這個地方看起來不錯
This place looks perfect.
-這簡直就是個垃圾場  -沒錯
- This place is a dump. - Exactly,
所以沒人會來這地方找你
and it's the last place anyone would look for you.
對啊  但是肝炎
Yeah, but it's the first place
肯定會來這找我
that hepatitis would look for me.
好吧  這只是暫時的
Okay, this is only temporary.
你保持低調  我來幫你解決
You lay low, and I will straighten this out.
我究竟憑什么要相信你
Why in God's name would I trust you?
沃頓  我知道以前給你
Look, Walden, I know that I've caused you
造成了一些小困擾  但是
some tiny problems in the past, but...
你說小困擾嗎
Wha...? Tiny?
你假裝懷孕嚇走了我女朋友
You pretended to be pregnant to scare my girlfriend away.
你讓那只瘋狂的雪貂攻擊我
You sicced rabid ferrets on me!
你把我綁在床上
You tied me to my bed
試圖用吹葉機猥褻我
and tried to violate me with a leaf blower!
你真貼心  居然都記得
It's so sweet you remember everything.
但是現在我可以彌補過去的事情
But I can make up for all of that now.
你看  下水道堵了要找水管工
Look, when your sink is clogged, you call a plumber.
車子壞了要找修車工
When your car breaks down, you call a mechanic.
當一個危險的變態跟蹤你時
When you have a dangerous psychopath after you,
你要找我
you call me.
好吧
All right, fine.
我要殺了艾倫
I am gonna kill Alan.
如果你活過了今晚  可以找拉里雇的殺手
Oh, if you survive tonight, you should hire Larry's guy.
他很出色
He's good.
就是這里了
Here you go.
這是你們這里最好的房間嗎
This is, uh, this is the best room you got?
這間是總統套房
It's the presidential suite.
哪國的總統
The president of what?
斯洛伐克鳥國嗎
Crap-o-slovakia?
我可以給你提供蜜月套房
I could offer you the honeymoon suite.
如果你聞得慣"愛情的味道"的話
You know, if you don't mind the smell of love.
不了  這里
No, no... this is, uh...
這里就行
this is fine.
你們有客房服務嗎
Do you, uh, do you have room service?
我這里或許有你想吃的"東西"
I might have something you might want to eat.
我不想吃
I don't think you do.
聽著  如果有人來打聽我
Listen, uh, if-if anyone comes here asking about me,
就說我不在這里
I-I'm not here.
別擔心
Don't worry.
永遠不會有人找到你
No one will ever find you.
如果等會你寂寞了
Hey, uh, if you get lonely later on,
我就在樓后面的公寓里
I'm in the apartment behind the building.
好  我知道了
Yeah, okay.
我家也沒什么好東西  但我有些好大麻
It's nothing fancy, but I've got some good weed
還有水療浴缸
and... a spa tub.
我都記住了
I'll, uh, keep that in mind.
14頻道在播《生存恐懼》
There's a Live Feed on channel 14
喜歡就看看
if you want to check it out.
這下可好  還得躲著他了
Great, now I got to hide from him, too.
沃頓這家伙會后悔當初偷了我的女友
This Walden guy is gonna regret the day he stole my girlfriend.
這不是偷
Oh, it's-it's not stealing.
應該算是借
It-It's more like borrowing.
-就像租車一樣  -可當你租車后
- Like-like renting a car. - Yeah, but when you rent a car
知道以前有其他男人在里面坐過
you know there's been other guys inside it,
扭扭凸起的把手  擺弄擺弄座位
turning the knobs, playing with the seat,
-還把東西塞進后備箱  -好了  好了
- shoving stuff in the trunk. - Okay, okay,
這個類比不恰當
maybe that's a bad analogy.
但你去找他對質
But that doesn't change the fact
也于事無補
that going over there to confront him
更不會改變事實
is not gonna help anything.
你有更好的主意嗎
You got a better idea?
我有
Uh, I-I do.
不如你忘記林賽
How about you forget about Lyndsey
咱們去酒吧泡妞
and we go out to a bar and pick up some women.
拉里和杰夫出外活動
You know, Larry and Jeff out on the prowl.
杰夫  很感謝你一番好意
Jeff, I appreciate what you're trying to do.
但恐怕如果我不這樣做
But I'm afraid if I don't do this,
我就永遠無法安心
I won't be able to live with myself.
恐怕你這樣做
And I'm afraid if you do this,
我就永遠無法安生了
I'll have to live by myself.
不  14頻道
Oh, no! Channel 14!
老天
Oh, God!
誰啊
Who is it?
拉里  我是來殺你的  沃頓
It's Larry, I'm here to kill you, Walden.
沃頓先生已經死了
Mr. Walden, he die.
我是打掃衛生的
I clean room.
不  小傻瓜  是我
No, silly rabbit, it's just me.
什么  是羅斯嗎
Wha...? Rose?
是...
Is that...?
你一個人嗎
Are you alone?
是  但剛才有個好人邀請我去泡水療浴缸
Yeah, but a nice man did just invite me into his spa tub.
我買了些吃的
Here, I brought some food.
-我不能吃東西  -為什么
- Yeah, I can't eat. - Why not?
如果我吃了
Well, because if I do,
最終就會去那里
eventually I'll have to go in there.
打死我都不會進去
And I'm not going in there.
有什么新情況嗎
Uh, so, did you find anything out?
還是沒找到拉里  他去哪里都有可能
Still no sign of Larry. He could be anywhere.
老天  艾倫應該處理好這件事的
God, Alan was supposed to take care of this.
是啊  他還告訴你他只會
Well, yeah, he also told you he was only gonna live
在你家住幾天  但現在已經過去了八百
and here we are at day 800 and...
四十三天
43.
我差點忘記了
Oh, I almost forgot.
我買了巧克力條
I got us some candy bars.
椰子口味是你的  這是你的最愛
Mounds for you, 'cause it's your favorite.
杏仁是我的
Almond Joy for me
你也知道  果仁嘛[瘋子]
'cause, you know... nuts.
你為什么對我這么好
Hey, why are you being so nice to me?
我得承認你傷害過我
You know, I'll admit that you hurt me.
我也做過不光彩的事情
And I did some things that I'm not proud of.
但就因為你申請了針對我的
But just because you took a restraining order
限制令
out against me...
并不代表我可以限制自己對你的感情
doesn't mean that I can restrain my feelings for you.
這是我聽過的
That is the sweetest,
最甜蜜最恐怖的話
most terrifying thing I've ever heard.
你真的怕我嗎
Are you really scared of me?
我在這房間里碰到的人  你都不算最恐怖的
You're not even the scariest person I've met in this room.
事實是  我也有錯
And the truth is, I'm-I'm not blameless.
我選擇了其他的女生
I mean, I chose another girl over you,
但看現在是誰陪在我身邊
and look who's here with me now?
我從未真正離開過你
I never really left you.
還真是這樣
Literally.
我知道我會后悔的
File this under things I'm gonna regret.
見鬼  應該把吹葉機帶來
Damn it, should've brought my leaf blower.
門鈴沒用
Oh, uh, the doorbell doesn't work.
什么
What?
我是說這樣沒用
I mean, uh, that-that does not work
如果你想來個強勢登場的話
if you want to send a message that there's a man here.
叮當
Ding-dong.
我要踢你屁屁
"I'm gonna kick your tushie."
有道理
You're right.
聽我說  可能不好收場
Okay, now, listen, now-now, this could get crazy.
可能會互相進行人身攻擊
I mean, there's gonna be a lot of name calling--
混蛋  白癡  艾倫
uh, uh, jerk, uh, idiot, uh, Alan.
-拉里  -林賽
- Larry? - Lyndsey?
你和沃頓·施密特的事
I know exactly what's going on
老子一清二楚
between you and Walden Schmidt.
他在哪里
Now, where is he?
哇  好漂亮的房子
Wow! This house is amazing.
拉里  不是你想的那樣
Larry, this isn't what you think.
就是我想的這樣
It's exactly what I think.
我有照片
I have pictures.
我們現在站在他的家
We're standing in his house!
是時候告訴你真相了
Okay, it-it's time for me to tell you the truth.
別相信她  她是個酗酒的劈腿蕩婦
Don't believe her! She's a cheating, drunk whore!
拉里  聽我說
Larry, listen to me.
我不是來和沃頓·施密特上床的
I'm not here to sleep with Walden Schmidt.
我是來這里和其他人上床的
I'm here to sleep with someone else.
-什么  -什么
- What?! - What?!
還記得你跟我說過
Remember you told me
你的性幻想就是看到我和別的女人在一起嗎
your fantasy was to see me with another woman?
-怎樣  -怎樣
- Yeah? - Yeah?
我做了安排  令你的夢想成真
I've arranged for your dream to come true.
-是嗎  -是嗎
- You did?! - You did?!
對  所以我才從沃頓·施密特手中
Yes, that's why I rented this beautiful beach house
租下這間漂亮的海邊別墅  作為生日驚喜
from Walden Schmidt as a birthday surprise.
我還準備了其它的驚喜
I also got us something else.
在旁邊觀戰的是哪一個
So, which one is watching us?
如果是他  我要加錢
If it's him, I'm gonna have to charge extra.
等等  這是真的嗎
Wait a minute. Is this for real?
生日快樂  寶貝
Happy birthday, baby.
3P
A threesome.
好大的禮啊
That is quite a gift.
時間倉促
Well, it was last minute,
我必須想出點什么
and I had to think of something.
一件漂亮的羊毛衫不算厚禮嗎
A nice cardigan wouldn't have done the trick?
老天  我覺得自己好蠢
God, I feel so stupid.
我甚至雇了人跟蹤你
I even hired someone to follow you.
你打電話讓他們走人吧
Well, why don't you call them off,
我們進去坐下來
and we'll all go sit down
好好談談你想看到的事情
and talk about the things you want to see?
再見  杰夫
Bye, Jeff.
Yeah, bye, Jeff.
我會寄給你一份視頻拷貝
I'll send you a copy of the video.
等等  這個  等等  這個
Wait. Thi-Thi... Wait. This is
是真的嗎
really... happening?
你是說  你和她嗎
I mean, you-you-you and-and-and her?
還有  還有他嗎
And-and... and him?
還有  在這里嗎
And-and-and here?
而  而我
While... while I...?
這招太賤了
Son of a bitch!
真是瘋了
This is crazy.
我打賭
You know, I'll... I'll bet
如果林賽真的是偷漢子了
if Lyndsey had been sleeping with somebody else,
那個男的現在一定非常非常生氣
he'd be really, really mad.
我知道  是不是好棒  杰夫
I know. Isn't this great, Jeff?
她不是劈腿的蕩婦  她只是蕩婦而已
She's not a cheating whore. She's just a whore.
你好  我是拉里·馬丁
Hi. It's Larry Martin.
是你啊
Oh, hey.
我不再需要你的服務了
Listen, I'm not going to be needing your services anymore,
很感謝你的幫忙
but I appreciate all your help.
不客氣
No problem.
我很榮幸
It was my pleasure.
再見
Good-bye.
艾倫打來的
That was Alan.
他說了什么
What did he say?
他感謝我保護你
Well, he, uh, thanked me for protecting you.
但還是沒找到拉里
But there's still no sign of Larry.
只要他還不知所蹤  你就不安全
And as long as he's out there, you're not safe.
我去買點必需品
I'm gonna go get us some supplies.
別走
No, don't go!
我們這么開心
We're having a good time.
你真是黏人的小可愛啊
You're just a sticky little honey bun, aren't you?
千萬別試圖聯系任何人
Now, don't try to get in touch with anyone,
否則拉里會殺了你
or Larry will kill you.
親親
Kisses.
我得去廁所了
I got to go to the bathroom.
媽的  我就尿床好了
Screw it. I'll just pee the bed.
羅斯
Rose?
別鬧了  羅斯
All right, come on, Rose.
這樣不好玩
This... this... It's not funny.
拉里
Larry?!
聽我說  我們可以說清楚的
Listen, we can... we can... we can work this out!
只是一點小誤會
It's-it's just a little misunderstanding.
老天  我...
Oh, God! I...
真沒禮貌
Well, that was rude.
看來我的澡白洗了
Looks like I took a shower for nothing.
無論你在哪里  出來吧  出來吧
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
我恨你  杰夫·斯壯曼
I hate you, Jeff Strongman.